http://www.friendshiptravel.com/privacy-policy.html

We use cookies to enhance your visit to our site. By using our website, you agree that we can place cookies on your device.		Close
BOOK NOW
WHERE WE GOAsiaAustriaBarbados CaribbeanCape Verde IslandsCroatiaCubaCyprus IslandCzech RepublicDominican RepublicEgyptFranceFuerteventura GreeceJordan TourKenya AfricaLanzaroteMalta & Gozo IslandsMontenegroMoroccoPortugalSaint Lucia CaribbeanSpainTenerifeTunisiaTurkey UKUSALATE BREAKSTYPE OF HOLIDAYChillaxLuxuryBeachSummerSightseeingWinterCruiseWalkingChristmas & New YearSki & Snow BoardFAQsNEWSLETTER SIGNUPCOVID TESTSBROCHURESFIRST TIME?YOUR BOOKINGCONTACT
Destination
All Destinations
Vietnam Asia
Austria - Niederau, Austria
Austria
Barbados Caribbean
Cape Verde Islands
Croatia - Brac Island
Our PP at Friendship Travel
What does Friendship Travel do with the information collected?
Where is my personal information stored?
How will I know if you change this privacy policy?
What about the other sites you link to?
Data Protection information
Consent information
What does Friendship Travel do with the information collected?
When you browse the site, we do not collect personal information about you. The only way we can collect any kind of personal information is if you give it to us.
To book a holiday with us, we will need to collect information about you to deal with your booking as smoothly as possible. This information may include such details as your name, your address and your credit card details. We disclose your information to third parties only for the purpose of completing your transaction with us, providing the above services to you and for the purposes of associated administration and obtaining professional advice.
Friendship Travel may use the information provided by you to contact you about your holiday.
Friendship Travel may also use this information to contact you with details of other products and services offered by other Friendship Travel Ltd Group companies, or which are available to Friendship Travel customers from its selected trading partners.
If you would prefer your information not to be used in this way, you should tick the box on the Payment Details page indicating this. If you would like to change your preference, want any further information or have any queries, please contact us at:
Friendship Travel Enkalon Business Centre Antrim N Ireland BT41 4LJ
When you view our site by linking from another web page we may store the name of that web page for purposes of internal administration. Also please note that any contact with Friendship Travel, either online or by telephone, may be recorded for training and monitoring purposes.
Where is my personal information stored?
All personal information is stored in secure databases at secure addresses to prevent unauthorised access.
How will I know if you change this privacy policy?
Any changes to the Privacy Policy will be made to this page. Your continued use of this site will constitute your agreement to the changed Terms and Conditions of using this site.
What about the other sites you link to?
Friendship Travel, its employees, contractors, agents, and owners are not responsible for the privacy policies or content of any websites which it may link to. Also ATOL protection does not apply to any non-member ATOL websites to which we link.
Data Protection information
In the UK we operate and are registered in accordance with applicable data protection legislation. We take full responsibility for ensuring that proper security measures are in place to protect your information. We must pass the information on to the relevant suppliers of your travel arrangements such as airlines, hotels, transport companies etc. The information may also be provided to security or credit checking companies, public authorities such as customs/immigration if required by them, or as required by law. With effect from the 5th March 2003 the US and UK government, customs and immigration authorities will require access to passenger information by airlines. Other countries may follow in future. Please be aware that any of your information held by the airlines will be available to the authorities.
Additionally, where your holiday is outside the European Economic Area (EEA), controls on data protection in your destination may not be as strong as the legal requirements in this country. We will not however, pass any information onto any person not responsible for part of your travel arrangements. This applies to any sensitive information that you give to us such as details of any disabilities, or dietary/religious requirements. (If we cannot pass this information to the relevant suppliers, whether in the EEA or not, we cannot provide your booking. In making this booking, you consent to this information being passed onto the relevant persons).
You are entitled to a copy of the information held by us. If you would like to see this please contact us. We may make a small charge for this.
Consent information
By disclosing your personal information to us using this website or over the telephone, you consent to the collection, storage and processing of your personal information by Friendship Travel as stated in this Privacy Policy
Ok
The air holidays and flights on this site are ATOL protected by the Civil Aviation Authority license 6683
Loyalty SchemeHoliday ExtrasLinks on Friendship Travel web siteTerms and conditionsPrivacy PolicyAccessibility statement Holidays for Singles over 40'sSingles HolidaysSingles Holidays for over 50’sSolo HolidaysblogSingles Holidays Over 60
Design by White Gate Design.
Website and online bookings by Metafour
